const mondai = [
    { number: 1, question: '586 + 547 =', answer: '1133', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 2, question: '836 + 897 =', answer: '1733', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 3, question: '675 + 758 =', answer: '1433', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 4, question: '936 + 997 =', answer: '1933', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 5, question: '759 + 667 =', answer: '1426', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 6, question: '819 + 876 =', answer: '1695', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 7, question: '896 + 947 =', answer: '1843', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 8, question: '849 + 876 =', answer: '1725', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 9, question: '729 + 894 =', answer: '1623', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 10, question: '865 + 969 =', answer: '1834', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''}
];